Onslaught v 2.2 by Xslaught
Windows Mugen 04.14
---------------------------

Profile
-------
Name: Onslaught
Original game: Marvel vs Capcom

Moves
-----

Onslaught (1st Form)

[ Specials ]
Sentinel Force:			a/b/c/x/y/z
Sentinel Assist:		b + y
Hyper Grav:				F, D, DF, x/y/z
Magnetic Tempest:		D, DF, F, x/y/z
Hyper Rush:				D, DF, F, a/b/c
Teleport (Backward):	D, DB, B, a
Teleport (Center):		D, DB, B, b
Teleport (Forward):		D, DB, B, c
Form Switch:			start					*training mode

[ Hypers ]
Magnetic Shockwave:		D, DF, F, a+b/a+c/b+c
*1 power level
Hyper Mind Blast:		D, DF, F, x+y/x+z/y+z
*1 power level
Sentinel Summon:		D, DB, B, a+b/a+c/b+c
*2 power levels

Onslaught (2nd Form)

[ Specials ]
Sentinel Force:			a/b/c
Claw Crush:				x/y/z
Rushing Arm:			D, DF, F, x/y/z
Hyper Grav:				F, D, DF, x/y/z
Mind Blast:				D, DF, F, x/y/z
Taunt:					start					*non-training mode
Form Switch:			start					*training mode

[ Hypers ]
3 Mind Blast:			D, DF, F, x+y/x+z/y+z
*1 power level
5 Mind Blast:			B, DB, D, DF, F, x+y/x+z/y+z
*2 power levels

Sentinel

[ Basics]
- standing
XCOTA SLP				hold B + x
MVC2 SLP				x
XCOTA SMP				y
MVC2 SMP				x (combo)
XCOTA SSP/MVC2 SSP		z
Rocket					hold F + z
XCOTA SLK/MVC2 SMK		hold B + a or a (combo)
XCOTA SMK				b
XCOTA SSK				hold B + c
MVC2 SSK				c
- crouching
XCOTA CLP				hold B + x
MVC2 CLP				x
XCOTA CMP				y
MVC2 CMP				x (combo)
XCOTA CSP				hold F + z
MVC2 CSP				z
XCOTA CLK				hold B + a
MVC2 CLK				a
XCOTA CMK				b
MVC2 CMK				a (combo)
XCOTA CSK				hold B or hold F + c
MVC2 CSK				c
- aerial
XCOTA ALP				hold B + x
MVC2 ALP				x
XCOTA AMP				y
XCOTA AMP down			hold D + y
MVC2 AMP				x (combo)
XCOTA ASP				hold B or hold F + z
XCOTA ASP down			hold D + z
MVC2 ASP				z
XCOTA ALK				hold B + a
MVC2 ALK				a
XCOTA AMK				b (hold dir to change direction)
MVC2 AMK				hold U + b or a (combo)
XCOTA ASK				hold B or hold F + c
XCOTA ASK down			hold D + c
MVC2 ASK				c

[ Basics - Alternate]
- standing
XCOTA SLP				hold B + x
MVC2 SLP				x
XCOTA SMP				hold B + z
MVC2 SMP				y
XCOTA SSP/MVC2 SSP		z
Rocket					hold F + z
XCOTA SLK/MVC2 SMK		hold B + a or b
XCOTA SMK				hold B + b
XCOTA SSK				hold B + c
MVC2 SSK				c
- crouching
XCOTA CLP				hold B + x
MVC2 CLP				x
XCOTA CMP				hold B + z
MVC2 CMP				y
XCOTA CSP				hold F + z
MVC2 CSP				z
XCOTA CLK				hold B + a
MVC2 CLK				a
XCOTA CMK				hold B + c
MVC2 CMK				b
XCOTA CSK				hold F + c
MVC2 CSK				c
- aerial
XCOTA ALP				hold B + x
MVC2 ALP				x
XCOTA AMP				hold B + z
XCOTA AMP down			hold D + y
MVC2 AMP				y
XCOTA ASP				hold F + z
XCOTA ASP down			hold D + z
MVC2 ASP				z
XCOTA ALK				hold B + a
MVC2 ALK				a
XCOTA AMK				b (hold dir to change direction)
MVC2 AMK				hold U + b
XCOTA ASK				hold B or hold F + c
XCOTA ASK down			hold D + c
MVC2 ASK				c

[ Specials ]
Rocket Punch:			D, DF, F, x/y/z			*can be done in air
Sentinel Force:			D, DF, F, a/b/c
Fly:					D, DB, B, x+y/x+z/y+z	*can be done in air
Grab:					D + x/y/z 				*on downed opponent

[ Hypers ]
Plasma Storm (XCOTA):	D, DF, F, y+z
Plasma Storm (MVC2):	D, DF, F, x+y/x+z
Hyper Sentinel Force:	D, DF, F, a+b/a+c/b+c
Hard Drive:				D, DF, F, x+y/x+z/y+z	*in air

Open Source Policy
------------------
This character is open source. I'd say if you use snippets of code then don't feel obligated to give credit.
If 50%+ of the material is used then I'd appreciate credit. This means please leave credit if you use a chunk of stuff.
There is no need to ask for permission.

Notes:
------
There are three stages included with this archive that will display Onslaught's 2nd form behind the floor. Only these stages will show him properly.
- new_york_city_skyline
- xmvsf_apocalypse_now
- mshvsf_apocalypse_now

Credits
-------
Serious Cat:			For the palettes and custom intros
╔════════════════════════════╗
║ ____                       ║
║/0○Oo\  Palettes by N8      ║
║\_   0\ I.M.T.: SrsC@       ║
║  \O__/ M.F.G.: Kula Diamond║
║ Web: The Dragon's Mouth    ║
║    http://n8space.webs.com ║
╚════════════════════════════╝
Doorhenge:				He gave me permission to modify Apocalypse's stage to interact with Onslaught.
Phantom of the Server:	His works are stated to be open source and I saw he made Onslaught's stage from Marvel vs Capcom. I figure it'll save some time to
						just modify what he had done. The stage sprites were reripped with WinKawaks and reduced with the optimized octree method.
Winane:					For the AI activation code and the training mode detection code which appears to not have been archived.
						AI activation code: http://www.mugenguild.com/winane/tutorial/index.html
						Training mode detection code: http://michaeldgames.com/Mugen/chars/zeeky/States/State-2.ST		      
VIB:					For the Stage interaction code.
						http://mugenguild.com/forumx/index.php?topic=9773.0
Kong:					For some of Sentinel's missing sprites I didn't rip
ETG:					For the MVC2 Hyper Combo Finish BG sprites
Shulbocka:				For the Sentinel Big Portrait
Redhot:					For the MVC2 Effect sprites
Luigi Master:			For the MVC2 Effect sprites
Mugenguild:				The coding forum has been of great use
Infinity Mugen Team:	For the EOH template which I took snippets from
RandomSelect:			The forum was informative for the defence data
Capcom:					For creating Marvel vs Capcom for which the sprites and sound files were obtained from.
Marvel:					For creating Onslaught
Elecbyte:				For creating Mugen
Artmoney:				Without this tool, the work would have been much more tedious.
Winkawaks:				Self explainatory

Changes 07.30.09
----------------
Note that the only difference between Sentinel and Onslaught are:
Statedef 5150, Statedef 5500, config.txt, sentinel.def, the SFF file is reduced, and the intro is left out and ending is different.

[x] Added config.txt
[x] Added custom intros by Serious Cat
[x] Fixed Hyper Grav Damager to destroy itself - no more invisible attack when there are no orbs left
[x] Fixed Onslaught 2nd form continue screen
[x] Fixed First attack message
[X] Sentinel's Aerial D+MP is now able to move left/right
[x] Fixed Time over for Sentinel
[x] Fixed Time over for onslaught 1 and 2
[x] Air guard while flying returns Sentinel back to flying state
[x] Increased Clsn1 box for Hyper Rush
[x] Dash punch may not always work - I just added a constant velset for vel x. Unsure if it'll fix it
[x] Fixed hitspark xy for Hyper Mind Blast
[x] Fixed hitspark xy for Magnetic Tempest
[x] Fixed hitspark xy for Sentinel SLP, MVC2 SLP, MVC2 SMP, MVC2 SSK
[x] Made it so Advance Guard should work against small characters
[x] Fixed it so helpers parents are not destroyed before child.
  - Hyper Sentinel Force
  - Plasma Storm
  - Sentinel Force - Strong
  - Magnetic Shockwave
  - Hyper Grav
  - Sentinel Force - Onslaught
  - Intro/Taunt - Rocks
  - Rensha Beam
[x] Fixed debug overflow for Helper(20300) (head)
[x] MVC2 SSK - removed ownpal = 1 from Explods
[x] Added anti-spam attack. Onslaught's gethit anim threshold increases each time his gethit anim takes place and decreases when he's not in a gethit state
[x] Removed life point handicap since some character's default life is above 1000.
[x] Fixed Sentinel's dash back with using 2 punches + holdback so it won't cancel into dash fwd
[x] Reduced scale of dash explod to 0.5, 0.5
[x] Removed dash dust from dashs
[x] Removed dash explod from dash back
[x] Made it so specials and hypers can be cancelled into regardless of movecontact
[x] Changed ticks (dimming) of Floor for MSHvSF Apocalypse Now! within onslaught.air from 11 ticks to 13 ticks.
[x] Adjusted HyperBg so it turns black first then shows the HyperBG.
[x] Added missing MVC2 HyperBG sound.
[x] Removed Launch capability of Sentinel's Standing Medium Kick (Grenade Kick).
[x] Super Jump after launcher can be initiated with holdfwd.
[x] Added cornerpush to Standing Medium Kick (Grenade Kick) for balance.
[x] AnimElemNo 24 (start) of punch for onslaught (2nd form) is now guardable
[x] Added shadowoffset of -1 to Sentinel
[x] Lowered position of super jump explod to 30.
[x] Added 2 BG music (1 for each form) - This was a ridiculous request as it increased the .snd file to about 41.9 MB but it makes it more enjoyable.
	- In the case of multiple Onslaughts, player 2 trumps the others. This works if P1 is Onslaught. I don't want to work through the logic for P1 not being Onslaught with team(s) of Onslaught.
[x] Removed debug overflow for Onslaught (1st Form)'s Hyper Mind Blast
[x] Alternate command set for Sentinel - so you can use all 6 buttons to do an aerial rave.
[x] Fixed it so sound 5, 15 (gethit animtype of 3-5) plays for Sentinel
[x] Aerial advance guard fixed
[x] Advance guard explod scaled to 0.5, 0.5
[x] Make bubble win pose match over only
[x] Hyper Grav orbs no longer can be attacked with any attack to remove them. There was an issue where the Clsn1 box would not reach the gethit Clsn2 box.
[x] Changed HyperGrav P2 Custom State's AnimExist trigger to SelfAnimExist.
[x] Realigned Special Dust to 5, -10 instead of 17, -17 and increased the speed of it.
[x] Fixed Sentinel Throw bug against Super Armor opponents
[x] Improved resurrection code slightly - Bigger Clsn1 box for Invisible Projectile and uses damage to give life instead of TargetLifeAdd.
[x] Added a failsafe code incase Onslaught (2nd Form)'s Dash punch does not reach BackEdgeDist for certain stages.
[x] You can now press F1 to KO Onslaught. He recovers life in training mode.
[x] Onslaught (2nd Form) now can stay off the screen.
[x] Sentinel's Bubble Win Pose should work with other Sentinels not by me. It still won't work with Sentinel by me.
[x] Added option for timer freeze.
[x] Var(50) no longer persists. Form changes rely on Var(51).

Changes 06.05.09
----------------
[x] - Removed Onslaught from showing for Sentinel's continue screen - common.st
[x] - Removed ability for Sentinel to switch to Onslaught in training mode - onslaught.cmd
[x] - Removed cornerpush from MVC2 Plasma Storm. He didn't have it in MVC2. - sentinel.st
[x] - Added explosion sound for Sentinel Force and Sentinel Assist upon destruction. Wasn't in the original game. - onslaught1.st
[x] - Gave him lower hit priority (3, Miss) for
      - Hyper Rush - onslaught1.st
	  - Claw Crush - onslaught2.st
	  - Rushing Arm - onslaught2.st
[x] - Following moves are improved in terms of speed by removing ownpal = 1
    - Magnetic Shockwave - onslaught1.st
	- Magnetic Tempest - onslaught1.st
	- Sentinel - F+SP - Rocket Explosion. Removed all those unnecessary ownpal = 1 from the explods - sentinel.st
		- Unsure of how much it speeds gameplay up since I do not have a slow computer to test it.
[x] - Added ScreenBound for Hyper Grav Orbs - onslaught1.st
[x] - Depowered Sentinel's Super Armor a bit. - common.st
[x] - Amplified sounds by 10 Db - onslaught.snd
     - all except intro music and EOH template sounds
[x]- Fix Statedef 41 (Super Jump) from freezing - common.st
[x]- Fix Statedef 452 (MVC2 - Crouching Strong Punch) - sentinel.st
[x]- Change Command for Sentinel's U,D,z to hold D+z- onslaught.cmd
[x]- Speed up Magnetic Tempest - onslaught1.st - Unsure since I don't have a slow computer
     - Removed the ownpal = 1. Hopefully this will speed things up
[x] - Reduce sprites in Sentinel - sentinel.sff
[x] - Implemented failsafes for throws - sentinel.st
[x] - Medium throws - sentinel.st
[x] - Grab - throws - sentinel.st
[x] - Strong throws - sentinel.st
[x] - Added compatibility for Doorhenge's XMvsSF Apocalypse Now! stage - with permission - included - -2.st, onslaught2.st, onslaught.air, onslaught.sff
[x] - Added compatibility for my own MSHvSF Apocalypse Now! stage since I couldn't get in touch with KFM, I made my own.
[x] - Realign Sentinel Special Dust - sentinel.st
[x] - Fix Onslaught 2nd Form KO Pos Y - common.st
[x] - Fixed stage parallax effect for Onslaught's Sentinel Summon move - onslaught1.st
      - For NYC stage, the 2 Apocalypse Now! stage
[x] - Wall hit spark and sound for Sentinel himself - 5030 - common.st
[x] - Hit ground anim implemented for Sentinel himself - common.st, sentinel.st
[x] - Take damage for moves that attempt to put him in a custom state - -2.st
[x] - Rocket Punch - Hits "downed" (falling) opponents - sentinel.st
[x] - Reduced the frequency of Sentinel Force used by Onslaught's 2nd Form for his AI.
     - Changed Random < 50 to Random < 30 out of 1000. :-/ - onslaught.cmd
[x] - Increase Sentine's stun threshold and make it so he can't be stunned right after being stunned.
	 - Changed his threshold to 6000 instead of 3000. This is double the amount it takes for him to become dizzy.
     - common.st, -2.st, -3.st
[x] - Reduce damage values for XCOTA D A.SK
[x] - HitOverride fixed. Weird how NotHitBy accepts value of SCA to work for everything and HitOverride doesn't.
	- This fixes the opponent attempting to throw and failed.
[x] - Added missing "whiff" sound for Onslaught (2nd Form)'s punch
[x] - Added option for resurrection for whoever wants him to be cheaper :/
Giving the player his life back for resurrection is still in test. It's worked for me so far.
Go to Statedef 15000 - common.st

in common.st
remove the Null

[State 15000, Resurrection]	; Remove to remove resurrection
type = Null;ChangeState
trigger1 = !Var(50)
trigger1 = !Time
trigger1 = Life < (Floor(GetHitVar(damage)))
value = 15150
ignorehitpause = 1

[x] - By popular demand, separating his form has been implemented if you looked in the code.
in common.st

To play as only his 2nd form

Remove the Null for
[State 190, Onslaught (2nd Form) - Debug]
type = Null;VarSet
trigger1 = 1
var(50) = 1

To play as only his 1st form:

Remove the Null for
[State 190, Onslaught (1st Form) - Debug]
type = Null;VarSet
trigger1 = 1
var(50) = 0

Changes 06.01.09
----------------
Too many to list. I will name a few. This is a remake.
Reripped all sprites with optimized octree + nearest color reduction method.
Realigned all sprites. All should be aligned with perfect axis including effects except non-MVC/XCOTA sprites which I took from the EOH template.
Most of the velocities came from using Artmoney. The exception is MVC2 type moves which I have no idea how to get perfect velocity data from as of now.
Damage values were taken from Artmoney. However, for gameplay's sake, I adjusted some overly high damage values.
All sound effects were ripped fresh with Nebula Jukebox then trimmed with Audacity. The exception is the announcer sound effects from the EOH template.
His 2nd form is shown behind the stage for his own stage included with this character.

Contact
-------
I cannot guarantee how long these contact information will last.

E-mail:		xslaught@hotmail.com
			This is my spam mail account
Website:	http://mugen.codejin.com
			http://www.codejin.com