-----------||||||||||||||||	BLACK CAT	||||||||||||||||-----------
---------------------------------------------------------------------

Sprite Edits, Character design, Concepts ---->  XFields
Sprite Edits, Concepts ---->  Beja
Programming-Code ---->  O Ilusionista
Support ---->  Eclipse

---------------------------------------------------------------------

0.99 Stand alone release
	Tons of bugs fixed (air, cns, cmd)
	New FX and sounds
	Ground slam fx
	Souplet modified
	Dashing claws has a follow up
	2 new intros (one against Spiderman)
	Two modes: old and new. Open the Settings.cns and modify if you want the old version
	New move: Pokerface, a hyper done while she on the web.
	Heros 4 hire hyper move (lvl 3)


0.95 EOH version release - 
	Bugs fixed
	Basic Instinct Hyper added
	Some code tweaks
	MVC-like offscreen moves
	Maximum Cat can be controlled now
	Souplet finished


0.9 version release - 16/12/2008 (beta version)
0.4 			  - 2007 (leaked version XP)

---------------------------------------------------------------------

Name - Black Cat
Game origin -  Edited character
Version - 0.99
Projects this character belong:
- "MvsC3: Mugenesis of Heroes"


WINMUGEN  ONLY


---------------------------------------------------------------------
-----------|||||||||||||||| COMMAND LIST ||||||||||||||||------------
---------------------------------------------------------------------

---------------------------------------------------------------------
MISC
---------------------------------------------------------------------

F+P	air(edge)	Wall Jump

---------------------------------------------------------------------
GRABS
---------------------------------------------------------------------

PP	standing	Suplex
KK	standing	Leg Fetish
KK	air		Paparazzi Shot

---------------------------------------------------------------------
SUPERS
---------------------------------------------------------------------

DP+ K		standing	Lovely Necklace
QCF+ P	standing	Dashing Claws
QCF+ K	standing	Ceiling Blitz
QCB+ K	standing	Elevator Action
QCB+ P	standing	*Wall Climb (requires Stick Wall)
QCF+ P	air		Helpless Kitty

---------------------------------------------------------------------
WEB MOVES (Requires Stick Wall)
---------------------------------------------------------------------

Moving:
---------------------------------------------
FF		ON WEB		Foward Jump Wall Grab
BB		ON WEB		Backward Jump Wall Grab
F/B/U/D		ON WEB		Crawl on the web

Attacking:
---------------------------------------------
D+K	on web		Pretty Stomp
D+P	on web		Splendor Love

Web Hyper:
---------------------------------------------

QCF+PP	on web	Pokerface

---------------------------------------------------------------------
HYPERS
---------------------------------------------------------------------

QCF+PP	standing	Claws Barrage
QCF+KK	standing	Maximum Cat
QCB+PP	standing	Love Clamp
QCB+KK	standing	Cat Scratch Fever (lvl2)
QCF+PP	air		Basic Instincts

QCB+PP  while on SUPLEX	Souplet

x,x,F,a,Z standing	Heros 4 Hire (lvl3)


---------------------------------------------------------------------
SPECIAL HYPERS
---------------------------------------------------------------------

DD+PP	standing	BadLuck
	Random objects will fall from the sky, she is faster but less powerful

DD+KK		standing	Stick Wall (HumBug)
	Required to use Wall Climb moves. 


---------------------------------------------------------------------
-------||||||||||| CHARACTER PROFILE & BACKGROUND |||||||||||--------
---------------------------------------------------------------------

Real Name: Felicia Hardy
Current Occupation: Private Investigator
Dual Identity: The Black Cat
Place of Birth: Queens, New York
Height: 5'10"
Weight: 120 lbs
Eyes: Green
Hair: Platinum Blond

Felicia Hardy is the Black Cat, who first appeared in Amazing Spider-Man #194. 
She began a career in crime out of respect and adoration for her cat-burglar father, 
but kept it on as a misguided attempt to attract the attentions of Spider-Man. 
Felicia and Peter have been very close in the past, and she is fully aware of his secret 
identity.

Initially, Felicia's abilities were 100% natural, with the 'accidents' which seemed to 
befall those who crossed her path being merely well-planned stunts. After her near-death 
at the hands of The Owl and Dr Octopus in Spectacular #72, Felicia feared that her lack 
of powers made her a vulnerability to Spider-Man, and that she would lose him.

While Peter was away in Secret Wars, Felicia turned to Kingpin, and made a pact with him 
in return for his scientists giving her super-powers. She kept the secret from Peter for 
quite some time. What she didn't realize was that her newly-gained genuine 'bad luck' 
power was infectious, and that it was permanently jinxing Spider-Man. That of course was 
the Kingpin's plan all along.

She broke up with Spider-Man, and Doctor Strange removed her bad-luck power, changing her 
other abilities in the process. Since then she has settled into a life of her own, albeit 
one which regularly intertwines with Peter's. She dated Flash Thompson for a while, primarily 
to irritate Peter. Mary Jane and Black Cat have become close friends in spite of their once 
intense rivalry over Peter. Mary Jane has even asked Cat to search for Peter if he has been 
gone for too long as Spider-Man. Black Cat bought some nifty strength enhancing equipment 
from the Tinkerer, started Cat's Eye private investigation service and occasionally teams-up 
with Pete.

At some point, Black Cat - along with the mutant Wolverine - was kidnapped and forced to 
survive against multiple assailants on an uninhabited island. They managed to survive many 
traps, including the volcano in the middle of the island erupting, and tracked down the one 
who kidnapped them, Arcade. They easily tracked him down and left him tied up on in the 
Savage Land. 

During the Civil War resulting from the Superhero Registration Act, Black Cat accepted an 
offer from Misty Knight and Colleen Wing in the new Heroes for Hire, purely for the money. 
Felicia, along with her teammates, are assigned to apprehend any unregistered hero. 

---------------------------------------------------------------------
Powers and Abilities
---------------------------------------------------------------------

.Original Powers
Probability Field Manipulation: The Black Cat was once imbued with a genuine ability to cause 
"bad luck" by scientists working for the Kingpin through a bargain made with him. This power 
allowed her to subliminally affect probability fields, which would cause improbable, though 
not impossible, events of "bad luck" to occur to enemies within her line of sight. However, 
this ability was removed from her by Dr. Strange, though the process mutated her body and 
granted her certain feline abilities including superhuman agility, reflexes, infrared vision, 
and retractable claws. However, after being exposed to a device designed by the Chameleon to 
remove Spider-Man's powers, Felicia lost these abilities as well.

.Current Powers
The Black Cat currently possesses no superhuman abilities, though she does uses various high 
tech equipment and inventions of the Tinkerer that do give her various augmented abilities.

.Abilities
The Black Cat, without her costume, is an Olympic level athlete and is a highly skilled, 
Olympic level gymnast. She is also trained and well versed in several martial arts styles 
and is an accomplished and experienced thief.

---------------------------------------------------------------------
Equipments
---------------------------------------------------------------------
Black Cat Costume: The costume she currently uses was designed by the Tinkerer and is designed 
to increase many of her natural physical attributes.

    * Peak Human Strength: The Black Cat's costume increases her physical strength to levels 
beyond the natural limits of a woman of her weight and physical build. In fact, her strength 
is increased to the maximum of human potential, enabling her to lift approximately 800 lbs 
with maximum effort.

    * Superhuman Speed: The Black Cat's speed is similarly enhanced, though to levels that 
are slightly beyond the capabilities of the finest human athlete. Over short distances, she 
can sprint at a top speed of about 40 miles per hour.

    * Superhuman Agility: The costume she wears also possesses various implants. Without 
these implants, she has the agility of an Olympic level gymnast. However, the implants 
augment her natural agility to levels that are beyond the capability and physical limits 
of the finest human athlete.

    * Retractable Claws: The gloves of the Black Cat's costume contain retractable, metal 
claws at the tip of each finger. These claws are highly durable and razor sharp. They can 
also be fired from the gloves in the form of grappling hooks, with which she can scale large 
buildings with ease.

    * Transportation: A combination of traveling by foot across the roof tops and the use of 
wirepoons hidden in her gauntlets that when fired can attach to building ledges and flag posts 
by the use of miniature grappling hooks. These allow her to swing from building to building 
in a similar style to Daredevil.

Source: www.spiderfan.org
	  www.marveldatabase.com


---------------------------------------------------------------------
--------------|||||||||||||| WIP HISTORY ||||||||||||||--------------
---------------------------------------------------------------------

XFields:
When I first made a sprite edit of black cat, she was not cool as she is now.
When I first attempted to do a sprite for MVC3 she was more simple, a frankensprite between 
psylocke and spiral(and testament hair).Now she uses lots of bases.
She was a awesome character to work in and i learned lots with this experience.
I wish you all have a good time playing with her, and see you soon on next version.


Beja:
Back in 2006 I start to talk with XFields about join myself at ProjectX fan game. 
Them he started the development of BlackCat concept for MVC3, I like the design and ask 
to join forces with him.
Along this time BlackCat had a lot of problems involving Mugen Teams and some times I even
think of giving up on her but we get over it and now you can see what it becomes.
I hope all of you enjoy playing with her.

O Ilusionista:
I joined this later, after two attempts of finding a programmer to her. XF and Eclipse are
old buddies, that I drove crazy because I always made the things different from what they
wanted to, LOL. But that was for a good propouse, as you can see :)


---------------------------------------------------------------------
---------||||||||||| CREDITS AND SPECIAL THANKS  |||||||||||---------
---------------------------------------------------------------------

O Ilusionista thanks:

* XFields, Eclips and Beja, for obvious reasons :)
* Mauteck, to started this char
* SonSon3000 for his ID code
* my old buddy Loganir, for the ground slam fx code and sprites and the camera control.
* OrochiGill, for the bug report
* Cybaster, for the GREAT bug report. Many of the fixes are thanx to him.
* KOD for the KOF2k2um effects


X-Fields, Eclipse and Beja thanks:

* Eclipse for everything, without he, the char would be much more delayed.
  (I mean he helped in sprites, codes, moves,effects and in much more)
* X-boy for really useful helping hand at sprites
* Buyog for Patience and giving initial hope at programming her
* Ryou Win for friendship and good feelings about her
* Loganir for Constructive Criticism!
* Mauteck for bringing her to life at the 2nd time.
* To the people that didn't download the leaked version.
* Fervicante for giving us permission to use his characters sprites to edit.
* Ahrimanes for giving us permission to edit things over some sprites he made
  (But we didn't use them)
* Tammy Ryan for making the sweet voices you hear
* Ricco for letting me know about voice actors for hire
* Marvel for creating Black Cat and Spiderman
* Dc for Creating Catwoman and letting marvel inspire on it to create BlackCat
  (they will never admit it rsrs)
* Alrio, Ed Benes and Terry/Rachel Dodson for giving us those artworks you see.
* Everybody that contribute to turn this character into reality and we forgot to mention here
  (Sorry!!) 
* And you for downloading it!!

---------------------------------------------------------------------
Words:
---------------------------------------------------------------------
I hope all of you enjoy this version. It's much better than the one that was leaked 
some time ago.
It takes a lot of time to conclude this and the results are very close of what we imagine.
We know that is much more to do and things to improve, so we count on you to give us some
constructive feedback.


---------------------------------------------------------------------
-----------||||||||||||||| RECOMMENDATIONS |||||||||||||||------------
---------------------------------------------------------------------

* BlackCat is property of Marvel Comics 
* Don't host the character without authorization.
* Don't extract the sprites from SFF and try edit like it was yours.
* Permissions, modifications or anything related to it will be analised but you must 
contact us first.
* It can NOT be used for ANY COMMERCIAL PURPOSE


---------------------------------------------------------------------
-------------||||||||||||||| CONTACT US |||||||||||||||--------------
---------------------------------------------------------------------

XFIELDS > rafa.xfields@hotmail.com
BEJA > leandrobeja@uol.com.br
O Ilusionista > douglasbaldan@hotmail.com
